I was an elite soldier
in the vampire army.
A Death Dealer.
And I was good at it.
But I was betrayed.
Viktor, our leader
and the most powerful vampire...
...was not the saviour
he had led me to believe.
Suddenly, allies turned enemies.
The vampire Elders I had once protected
wanted me dead.
Then I found Michael Corvin.
Neither vampire nor Lycan,
Michael became a hybrid.
We retaliated, killed the Elders.
But then everything changed.
I was captured, not knowing that I was
carrying Michael's child.
Eve, our daughter,
the first pure-blood hybrid...
...whose blood could end the war...
...became highly sought after
by both vampires and Lycans alike.
My only choice was to hide her
from the world and from myself...
...so not even I could lead them to her.
I was an elite soldier
in the vampire army.
My only choice was to hide her
from the world...
...so not even I could lead them to her.
I have lived beyond my time.
Another new moon
in a thousand years of new moons...
...and I do not care to see it.
I have nothing.
My coven...
...my daughter...
- ...my love, all gone.
- Cut her off!
And soon, perhaps...
...my very existence.
- Selene's coming!
- I am hunted...
...by vampires and Lycans.
Now I am an outcast, a pariah.
- Put her down!
- Remember, he wants her alive.
Fire!
Come on, now. Fire!
You are an extremely difficult person
to keep track of.
I don't need you.
But thank you.
Any word with Michael?
- Stop tracking me!
- I'm not tracking you.
I'm looking for Eve.
Well, I'm the very last person
who could help you find my daughter.
Selene, listen to me.
The Lycans are moving again.
No, this is different.
They're organised.
They have a new leader.
- His name is Marius.
- I'm finished with this war.
Well, it's not finished with you.
They could have killed you...
...but clearly their mission
was to capture you.
Your daughter's blood, it's a prize.
And if they find her, if they use it...
- ...Marius's power will be limitless.
- Well, then I hope she remains lost.
I need you to deliver a message.
- Grunt if you understand.
- Unh, unh!
Tell your Marius...
...if he thinks he can extract
information from me...
...to locate my daughter, he can't.
I don't know where she is,
and I don't want to know.
Marius will find you.
Do you understand your message?
What is it?
Have you seen this before?
No...
...but we need to get it out.
Let's go.
Bravo one, over. Car approaching.
- Access cleared.
- Close the gates.
Commencing perimeter sweep.
Privilege to welcome you home at last,
sir.
Semira awaits you
in her private chambers.
Semira?
Where is Cassius?
The entire council will greet you,
of course, sir...
...but Semira requests
just a few moments.
And your name is?
Varga, sir.
I shall try to remember it.
...and act accordingly
because of this tragic...
Leave us.
Darling Thomas. It has been...
- ...how long?
- Decades.
Congratulations.
I gather you have a seat
on the council.
I could not be more proud.
It's a shame that your return is not
under more festive circumstances.
It is said that the Western Coven
was utterly destroyed.
Yes, it was.
It's a blessing
you escaped with your life.
Mm. Well, many did not.
There has been too much death
among our people.
These urns are all that remain
of our Budapest Coven.
Well, you have my condolences.
We are losing the war, Thomas.
If we stay as we are, our species
will be extinct within five years.
Does Cassius share your view?
The Lycans have regrouped,
replenished...
...and are resolved
to exterminate us.
Oh, surely, you're safe here.
The Eastern Coven is a fortress.
We are no longer
the coven you remember.
We have fewer Death Dealers
than ever before.
You seem to be surrounded
by new cadets.
Raw recruits, neither combat-ready
nor numerous enough...
...to repel a large-scale Lycan attack.
There has never been
a large-scale Lycan attack.
At least not a coordinated one.
There has never been a Marius.
Pains me to admit it,
but for the first time in my life...
...I genuinely fear for our future.
So, what is your plan?
Semira, you always have a plan.
This little mise-en-scene
you're performing has a purpose.
I am not a mind reader.
Kindly do an old vampire
the courtesy...
...of telling him why
he's been invited here.
Selene.
Come on. We need to keep moving.
There are safe houses
far closer than this.
I told you, they destroyed them.
It's different now. Come on.
But you signed her death warrant.
Of course. I despise her.
She killed Viktor. I was his regent.
Until he met Selene.
So you want her to hunt Marius?
I want her to train our new recruits...
...so we have 100 Death Dealers
hunting Marius.
Heh, heh. I doubt she will agree.
Her only concern is for her daughter.
Eve, the hybrid.
Unfortunately, the poor girl
is half Lycan.
It's a vampire's instinct
to condescend to Lycans...
...but they're not afraid to evolve.
Meanwhile,
we stagnate from 1500 years...
...of this damned "species purity"
nonsense.
Huh. And the irony is that Selene...
- ...is probably the purest of us all.
- So the rumour's true?
Her blood has elements
of the Corvinus strain?
She is special.
She brought my son back
from the dead.
- Her blood restarted his heart.
- Impossible.
I witnessed it myself.
She saved my son's life.
Viktor and Amelia.
Side by side for eternity.
You were very fond of Amelia,
if I remember.
- I need you to be my ally on this.
- She won't risk coming here...
...unless she gets an invitation
from the whole council.
And I could never solicit
such a request.
Cassius is protective of the old ways.
He barely tolerates my seat
on the council as it is.
But these are desperate times, Thomas.
And that is why you
must convince the council to invite her.
Ahh...
They arrive tonight.
Dawn alert. Sixty seconds to sunrise.
Marius, the pack leaders have arrived...
...and I told them to wait
for you in the war room.
Fighting like dogs, no doubt.
- I'll handle it. Thank you.
- All right.
- Go on, then.
- Right, right.
Come around, come around.
No! Listen to me.
We're gonna wedge them in.
That's what we do.
From this side and that side,
we just wedge them in...
- ...and squeeze them out.
- Wedge them in?
Is that your plan?
It's not gonna lead to anything.
- He's getting angry.
- Shut up!
Stop!
- Are you a slave?
- No.
Then don't behave like one.
Look at this map.
What do you see?
Do you see Lycans
fighting over scraps?
I'll tell you what I see.
Volhynia.
Nordgau. Thuringia.
The Lycan victories.
I see vampires dead.
I see entire regions annihilated.
But we will get no further
if we fight amongst ourselves.
We must not rest...
...until we have destroyed
their final sanctuary.
Together, we are strong.
And when we have the blood
of the hybrid girl...
...we will be invincible.
Gregor.
You have returned alone.
- We were taken by surprise.
- Where is Selene?
- She spared me.
- Why?
To deliver a message.
She wants you to know
that her daughter is gone forever...
...that you can never find her...
...because even Selene
doesn't know where she's been hidden.
Do you believe her?
I put a tracer in her companion.
Well...
...that means you're not
completely incompetent.
Try and stay still.
- What is it?
- It's some sort of bullet.
It's burrowing through you
faster than you can heal.
It's self-propelled.
That's what I was trying to tell you.
These Lycans are sophisticated.
I don't know if I can remove it in time.
Well, the least you can do
is attempt to sound reassuring.
I'm going to attempt not to kill you.
That will have to do.
To whom do you want us
to offer safe haven and amnesty?
- To Selene the Death Dealer.
- The same Selene who murdered Viktor?
I need no reminder, Cassius,
of what she has done.
Shame on you, sir.
I will not hear her name spoken again.
Cassius, I share your outrage.
Whatever has possessed you?
If we don't act decisively...
...the war will be at your gate
within a fortnight.
And that is precisely
where it will remain.
No Lycan pack would dare
to attack our coven.
Our defences would rip them apart.
An ordinary Lycan pack, perhaps...
...but Marius has gathered a force
far more powerful than any...
Unsubstantiated hyperbole.
You need Selene.
Her prowess, her leadership,
her intimate knowledge of Lycans.
And her combat skills
are second to none.
He's right, she is the most lethal
Death Dealer we've ever had.
But she killed one of her own.
Not only the most powerful
and respected of the Elders...
...her protector, who loved her
like his own daughter.
She cannot be trusted.
She has been judged.
Perhaps she can also be redeemed.
It pains me to say it,
but Thomas is right.
No warrior has proved herself
more in battle.
She would be invaluable
in our fight against Marius...
...perhaps even the pivotal element
to secure our victory.
If she can be found...
...and sets foot
within this precious coven...
...I will hold you, Semira,
personally responsible...
- ...for controlling her.
- Of course.
Intruder. Intruder. Intruder.
Intruder. Intruder.
Who sent you?
Drop it.
How'd you find us?
There are only a handful
of safe houses left.
The Lycans made it rather easy.
The council of the Eastern Coven
sent me to bring you in.
- For trial?
- No.
- For your safety, and ours.
- You cannot expect me to believe that.
Every single one of them
signed my death warrant.
- Times change.
- Vampires do not.
This is from your father.
Is it authentic?
It's his seal, his handwriting.
The council has offered you clemency
and granted us both safe haven.
- Why?
- Marius.
It is the council's humble request...
...that you train us
to defeat him and his army.
Move. Come on.
The signal's coming from this way.
Look, I understand you're reluctant...
...but as guests of the council,
we will be protected by law.
My father wouldn't lie,
and he holds no grudge.
He had no love for Viktor, either.
Intruder. Intruder.
- Lycans.
- Intruder.
- We must leave.
- You should accept the council's offer.
- For Eve.
- Eve does not want my help.
I know you want to protect her.
And if we destroy Marius...
...we destroy the greatest threat
to her safety.
Now.
Marius.
We just missed them.
I do not wish to hear
the word "just" again.
Either we have her or we have nothing.
Do you understand?
- Do you understand?
- Yeah.
Tango Charlie approaching.
All clear.
Perimeter secure.
- Welcome.
- Am I?
Our coven's resources
and weaponry are yours...
...to transform these raw recruits
into Death Dealers worthy of your name.
Varga will be your right-hand man.
He knows all our strengths
and weaknesses.
He is also our most prolific Lycan killer,
with over 40 confirmed kills.
- It's an honour.
- David, welcome.
- Thank you.
- To mark the safe arrival of our guests...
...I've arranged a little soiree
in the Winter Garden.
There's really no need. Thank you.
Nonsense. There's always a need
to indulge in pleasure.
In times of war...
...this coven needs moments
to celebrate.
The arrival of Thomas,
David and Selene...
...is reason aplenty to rejoice.
To us all.
It's good of you to offer us
sanctuary, Semira. Thank you.
It will be entirely my pleasure.
Tell me, is it true that her blood
brought you back to life?
Yes, it is.
I owe her everything.
But, if you'll excuse me,
my father requests my counsel.
Thomas was always such a bore.
Well, Semira's certainly
taken an interest in you.
Well, the interest is certainly
not mutual.
We need her protection.
On the contrary,
I think I need protection from her.
The Battle of the Peste.
We thought it would be
the one to end the war...
...the final conflict...
...but here we are still.
I hope you see my bid for clemency
for Selene for what it is.
Clemency
is the least you can offer her...
...after bartering her daughter
to the Lycans.
I lost so much during this war.
Believe me, I am haunted still
by all those I failed.
Well, then you must help me
protect her.
She has lost even more
than we can imagine.
And she's important to me.
Marius is out there...
...reeking of canine insolence,
plotting our downfall.
We do not need Selene to destroy him.
I am more than capable.
No, Varga, you are merely adequate.
It's fortunate that we're not forced
to rely on your skills for our survival.
That, my sweet...
...yet unimaginative bedfellow...
...is my area of expertise.
- I think you should...
- Don't think, Varga.
You'll hurt yourself.
There are other ways
to prove your devotion.
Piece by delicate piece...
...the puzzle will fall into place.
Oh, yeah...
Yeah...
Don't aim where the Lycan is.
Anticipate.
And remember,
a Lycan is never more vulnerable...
...than when he's in wolf form.
- What?
- That makes no sense.
In wolf form,
they cannot use weapons...
...and their thinking
becomes much more primitive...
...driven only by bloodlust.
- How many have you killed?
- I don't keep track.
I'm increasing Lycan speed
by 20 percent.
Please continue.
My pack's probed the Eastern Coven's
perimeter for weaknesses...
...and there are none.
And any direct assault
would trigger the lockdown...
...which makes the coven impregnable.
Even if we could break inside
without losing 90 percent of our force...
- ...they have fallback positions...
- This.
- ...that can be...
- Is this ready?
Yeah.
When we have the hybrid's blood...
...we launch against the Eastern.
Find Selene, and we find her daughter.
My own invention.
One of the first things
a Death Dealer must learn...
...is how to fight in a confined space.
Of course, the one thing...
...this training session lacks
is unpredictability.
Perhaps you'll indulge me
and give my students...
Uh, I should say your students.
--a lesson in combat's unpredictability.
It would not only honour us, but it
would be invaluable to their training.
- I don't...
- Please.
That's enough.
Gather round.
We are going to school you...
...in the true nature
of the Lycan warrior.
For the sake of this lesson,
our esteemed guest Selene...
...will play the role of Death Dealer
bravely defending our fortress...
...and I will take the role
of Lycan villain...
...here to destroy it.
Ladies first.
Impressive.
Come on.
Tonight's lesson:
Do not trust your opponent
to fight with honour.
They are Lycan. They have none.
Ah!
Don't move.
Nightshade.
Leeches into vampire cells,
usually fatal.
But for one with her strength,
there will only be pain...
...followed by paralysis.
I'll kill you.
UV bullets.
Did you honestly think
I would forgive you for killing Viktor?
Varga, you have orders.
Varga!
I don't need you to train Death Dealers.
I have Varga for that.
All that I need to rule this coven...
...and end the march of the Lycans
is your blood.
What about the bodies?
Sound the alarm.
Have the council find them.
Conclusive evidence of the atrocity
committed by Selene.
There's been a breach.
We need to find Selene.
- Cordoned off. Semira's orders.
- Step aside.
David.
Come.
There's more than one way
to move around this coven.
Amelia created these passageways
centuries ago.
Where does this lead?
To the private chambers,
including Semira's.
What the hell have they done to her?
Machina sanguinem exhauri.
Bloodletting.
Semira wants Selene's
most precious asset.
- This is gonna kill her.
- Eventually, yes...
...but it will be agonisingly slow.
Look.
This is designed to open the arteries
as wide as possible.
If we're not very careful,
we will do her more harm than good.
Careful.
Is this hers?
Yes.
Selene uses only
this particular weapon.
A known traitor within our walls.
This is precisely what I foresaw...
...and what you assured me
you would prevent.
Their blood is upon your hands.
- Sir, I did everything...
- Do not speak to me.
There can be no mercy.
I want her hunted
to the ends of the Earth.
It shall be done.
And I want her captured alive.
Is that understood?
Perfectly.
- We're running out of time.
- All right, take her.
You must go north, far north.
Var Dohr.
No.
Father and son united in treason.
Carry on with Selene.
I'll deal with them.
Oh...
Come on.
Go! Now!
No!
Dawn alert. Sixty seconds to sunrise.
Go ahead. The sun will burn you
to ashes out there...
...or you can die
with some grace in here.
They can walk in the sun.
You need to feed.
You've lost too much blood.
That child... Because he
helped that child of yours.
My son is dead. Dead.
David.
Take her now.
You must go north. Var Dohr.
Go! Now!
Thank you.
I'm very sorry
that you lost your father.
He put up a valiant fight.
It's strange to lose someone
you feel like you never really knew.
I feel the same about my mother, but...
I have almost no memory of her.
And I of Eve.
I didn't want her.
I didn't know her.
And now I've lost her.
Why do you insist on saying
that you've lost her?
She made me promise
I would never look for her...
...that I would never consider myself
having a daughter.
And she was right.
Nothing good has come
to anyone I love.
You're family,
and you're all I have left.
Well, then, you really are in trouble.
You need to rest.
Selene's clearly
in league with the Lycans.
Thomas and David were complicit
in this treachery.
They walked in the sun. This alone
is evidence of Lycan collusion.
Selene must be wiped from the pages
of our proud history.
Alexia.
- We shall avenge our fallen.
- See to it that you do.
- How much nightshade did you use?
- I thought it best to err on the side...
Varga, what have we said
about you thinking?
The poison will dissipate.
I need this blood untainted,
and I need it now.
It cannot be rushed.
It must run its course.
It's definitely the car.
But no sign of where they went.
Spread out across the city.
Search everywhere.
The train at
platform four terminates at this station.
Northbound.
I will be more powerful...
...than Cassius...
...than any vampire in this coven.
- What news of the search?
- Selene and David are heading north.
- Of course they are.
- Your Grace?
They will run to the only
remaining coven...
...to afford them safe haven:
Var Dohr, the Nordic fortress.
But Var Dohr is only a legend.
I would not give it
such an elevated status.
It is a frigid, dreary outpost
full of pathetic, peace-loving cowards.
You speak of it
as if you have actually been there.
Where do you think I was
when Viktor wasted years with Selene?
Prepare yourself.
The journey's long,
and I need you to take it alone.
I must be certain the traitor's there...
...before I risk sending a full squad
of Death Dealers so far from this coven.
You need to be more careful.
You need to be more gentle.
- Have you found Selene?
- Yes.
She is headed for the Nordic Coven.
I risk everything for this.
- For you, for us.
- I know, my love.
Semira grows more insane
for power with each day.
She must be stopped.
And every day, I fear more
what she will do if we are discovered.
I cannot attack the Eastern Coven
without the blood of the hybrid.
It's too strong, even for my horde.
Selene...
She is the key to the futures
of Lycans and vampires alike.
You shall have her.
Var Dohr is just beyond that ridge.
Where is everyone?
Watching.
We come seeking sanctuary...
...not to fight.
Then you've come to the right place.
My name is Lena.
Follow me.
What was that?
Some kind of trick.
You must be Selene.
Does the great Death Dealer
truly come in peace?
- I do.
- And what about this one?
This is David, son of Thomas.
Who I haven't seen
for many, many years.
You must excuse the attention.
Our coven doesn't receive
many guests, by design.
We do as we wish...
- ...not as others would have us do.
- And what of the Lycans?
We are too far removed
for them to take notice...
...and even if they did, our climate
is quite an obstacle to warm-bloods.
This coven wouldn't exist...
- ...without your mother's grace.
- You knew my mother?
All vampires do, my boy.
No. My mother was low-born.
She died giving birth to me.
A falsehood, you will find, designed
to keep your true lineage safe.
- Is she still alive?
- No.
And her death
was a terrible blow to our kind.
The mourning ceremony we held
lasted for an entire month.
Such an honour
is usually reserved for a high-born...
- ...a Grand Elder.
- Yes.
- Amelia.
How could a Grand Elder
have been my mother...
...and I not been told?
I have something for you.
Your father's greatest work,
infused with silver.
The Lycans will cower
from the very sight of it.
- It's beautiful.
- Thomas knew that one day...
...you would be beset
by enemies on both sides...
...and he was right.
David, this means that you are
the rightful heir of the Eastern Coven.
Your mother and father
spent many months...
...within the safety of these walls.
Viktor grew suspicious.
Then your father spirited you away...
...before Semira arrived
with her troops.
- And what of my mother?
- She returned to the Eastern Coven.
The light in her eyes...
Don't try and fabricate
some kind of martyrdom for her.
I prefer a more honest
appraisal of her decision.
She abandoned her only son
for the sake of her precious council.
- Take it.
- David.
David.
Amelia asked me to give him this.
What do you need?
Nothing. I just need to be left alone.
Yes, I know the feeling.
Why didn't my father
tell me about my mother?
I did not know your father well...
...but I know that his greatest fear
was to lose you.
It seems it's the curse of every parent
to disappoint their child.
- At least you fought for your child.
- Yes, and lost.
You have pure-blood heritage, David.
Your mother was an Elder.
Your parents kept you safe
for a reason.
They protected you
so that one day you could lead.
Your mother left you a gift.
That's very kind of you,
but I have no use for jewellery.
The ring is not the gift.
It contains the gift: a mother's love.
A single drop of her blood.
Maybe it'll help you decide.
You're just in time.
- Come.
- What is this?
- Valissa, the in-between place.
- Is she dead?
No.
She is...
...becoming.
She took a poison.
It allows her to visit the Sacred World.
When she returns,
she will see this world with new eyes.
I don't understand what this is.
We have long known
there is more than just this world.
When my father
first brought me down here...
...I felt as you do now...
...but I have since been
to the Sacred World many times.
My eyes see beyond the surface
of so many things.
- I see much about you.
- Such as?
I can see you've loved a Lycan...
...killed a vampire Elder
and given birth...
Stop.
I see you have lost your daughter...
...and how much pain
this gives you deep inside...
...where you will always hide it.
She's a special child.
Many battles will be fought...
...and lost over her.
- What else do you see?
- Darkness.
One that touches us all.
If you want to keep her safe,
you will need to go further...
...than even a warrior of your renown
has ever ventured before.
I have seen so much war...
...so much killing.
I cannot bear more.
The peace you will feel here is real.
It seeps into your skin
and comforts your soul.
Tell me about the Sacred World.
The water is the path.
Amelia!
I name our son David.
David.
One day, you will understand.
I'm so sorry.
Lycans! Sound the alarm!
Close the doors!
Move!
Just as I spoke of peace,
war has followed you here.
Protect your own.
I must find David.
- We have to get you away.
- No. We led the Lycans here.
We can't let these people die.
Run!
This way, men.
Go around that side.
There she is.
You parasite.
Just do it.
Marius.
At last.
- Aah!
- On your right!
I expected more from you.
Tell me where your daughter is.
I don't know.
Selene, all I want is her blood.
Only she can end this war.
I give you my word
she will not be killed.
What are you?
Tell him where she is and all this
butchery will be over forever.
I don't know.
Lies.
They've gone.
Michael.
- I freed you.
- Look at the eyes.
Who I am?
Do you not know who I am?
- My daughter.
- I don't want you.
Don't look for me.
She's telling the truth.
She doesn't know.
My time is done.
They are retreating.
I'm running out of time.
We must strike against
the Eastern Coven now.
You know what you must do.
Water is the path.
Selene.
Praise the day...
...when it ends.
Praise the ice...
...when it holds.
Praise the sword...
...when it kills.
Praise the life...
...that has lived.
It's time.
Power.
Such a seductively simple thing.
Either you have it all
or you have nothing.
How fascinating.
Amelia...
The water is the path.
You should stay here, David.
This can be your home.
Marius is heading east.
There's nothing stopping him now.
And my people are beset
with enemies on all sides.
How can I stay here and live...
- ...while they die?
- They need a leader.
Gate secure. Perimeter check.
Miss me?
- East gate is clear.
- West gate clear.
Commencing perimeter sweep.
Access granted.
What news do you bring?
A massacre.
The Lycans attacked
the fortress of Var Dohr.
Lycans in the north.
The Nordic Coven
was taken completely by surprise.
- Dozens of vampires have been killed.
- Was Selene amongst them?
Dead. Killed by Marius himself.
Wherever Selene goes,
trouble surely follows.
- What of David?
- I do not know.
I only wished I had arrived sooner.
I might have helped in some way.
Well, you've helped in so many ways.
You've done exactly as I hoped
and planned, if not more.
You see, information is power.
And I collect it with a passion.
Thank you for leading Marius
to the Nordic Coven.
Your Lycan lover...
...must be delighted
with his momentary success.
You thought I didn't know.
Foolish girl.
Dawn alert. Sixty seconds to sunrise.
The Lycan scourge
destroyed an entire coven.
To hide behind these walls
increases their advantage.
We cannot take the war to Marius.
Should we cower in the safety
of these walls...
- ...while he picks us off one by one?
- Curb your insidious comments, Semira.
This coven has held for 15 centuries.
- It will hold for 15 more.
- I hoped you would show strength...
...though I was willing
to settle for competence.
I was wrong.
What is the meaning of this?
If this council is too weak
to take action...
...it is my duty to do so.
You are relieved of your duties as
council members effective immediately.
The traitor returns.
Oh, you are a fool
to show your face here.
I will make you pay
for what you've done, Semira.
Marius and his army
are heading this way as we speak.
- I come to save my people.
- Your people? Heh.
Kill him. Kill him.
You aspire to be the protector
of your bloodline...
...yet you kill your own kind
in pursuit of power.
It ends now.
I am David,
son of the great Elder Amelia.
And I am the rightful heir to this coven.
Amelia had no son.
Well, she had the foresight...
...to know that my claim
would be challenged.
For the council.
Amelia.
His claim is true.
David is the last of the purebloods.
Irrelevant.
You are outnumbered and outgunned.
Varga, your orders still remain.
Kill him.
- I said, "Kill him."
- No.
You swore to serve me.
I swore to protect
the leader of this house.
Breach detected.
- Security system engaged.
- Lycans. They're here.
Lock her away until she can be judged
by the council.
Security system engaged.
Breach detected. Security system...
- She gets her damn war after all.
- Varga, you can still be forgiven.
Gag her as well.
Come on, move that truck. Move it.
Watch your angles!
Let's go!
Hold your positions.
- On the staircase!
- Behind you!
- Fall back!
- Retreat!
Behind the balustrades!
Take them out!
- Come on!
- Move, move, move!
Move it!
Fuck.
Aim at the ready!
Fire!
Hide from the light!
Run!
Move!
Shoot, shoot, shoot!
Impossible.
I saw you dead.
I'm here.
I brought backup.
There are too many of them.
I've already killed you.
Marius!
Marius. Please.
I wish your father
was alive to see this.
His ridiculous dream
of you ruling this coven...
...will be the very thing that kills you.
Missed.
Oh, it worked.
I'm one of you.
No! No! No!
You killed Michael.
This is the last of him.
You're family,
and you're all I have left.
Do you not know who I am?
Your leader is dead.
Take your wounded. Leave.
Leave!
We fought our greatest battle
in our darkest hour.
After centuries of war
between vampire and Lycan...
...this may at last be a time of peace.
We must once again
tend to our wounded...
...honour our fallen.
Our final two covens
must find strength and unity...
...to heal and rise from the ashes.
My journey has now come full circle.
Once an outcast, I am now
one of three chosen Elders.
From hunted to the highest honour.
I have lived a thousand years.
I may live a thousand more...
...or I may die tomorrow.
But I no longer fear death...
...for I have known it once already.
I am reborn...
...and my eyes have been opened
to the Sacred World...
...and to the promise
of what is yet to be.
There is no beginning.
There is no end.
There is only becoming.